Alright, we've taken a look at what it is that you're good at.
What skills you have and your educational background, so it's time to take a look at your work experience.
What kind of jobs have you had before?
Maybe you've just had college type jobs that maybe weren't necessarily career jobs.
Or maybe you have had some, feel like of a better word, "real jobs".
What you want to do is take a look at that work experience.
What did you gain from it?
Did you, you know, gain problem solving skills?
Did you gain customer service skills?
Don't just think in terms of "well I worked here".
What did you get out of that?
What did you learn from that job or from that work experience that will help you with you new employer, will help you get a job.
That's how you have to think about in terms of past work experience.